

# **Ming-Yang Ho**



ikaminyou@gmail.com

github.com/Kaminyou

in linkedin.com/in/kaminyou

+886 952792255

# Summary ·

A data scientist at aetherAI with 4+ years of experience in 2D/3D computer vision, natural language processing, machine learning, and deep learning algorithms development. Besides, I am also adept at web programming, cryptography, and clinical pharmacy.

## Skills

- Programming related
  - Python
  - PyTorch
  - •C/C++
  - ReactJS
  - MySQL
- Docker
- •Linux
- •Git
- Domain
  - Machine learning
  - Deep learning
  - •2D/3D computer vision
  - Natural language processing
  - Cyber security
  - Computer security

# Language •

- ·Mandarin (native)
- •English (TOEIC 825) [2014]
- Japanese (JEPT N1) [2021]

### **Interests**

Machine learning, Deep learning, Full stack development, Computer security

### Work experience

**Data Scientist** 

aetherAI, Oct. 2021 - (Current)

#### **Teaching Assistance (TA)**

NTU EE Machine Learning, Feb. 2021 - Jul. 2021

NTU EE Web Programming, Feb. 2021 - Jun. 2021

NTU CSIE Bioinformatics and Cheminformatics, Sep. 2020 - Jan. 2021

#### **Data Engineer Intern**

Dcard, Jun. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- •Built an automatic image cropping system to attract users' attention.
- •Invented a malicious applicants detection system with SimCLR.
- Established a system to immediately detect offensive comments.

#### Software Engineer Intern

Institute of Information Science, Academa Sinica, Jul. 2019 - Aug. 2019

•Leveraged the concept of RGB channels to assist in SNP prediction.

### Honors

#### 2021 PyCon APAC Speaker

Get 3D models out of nothing: Python implementation of deep learning-based 3D models reconstruction from 2D images..

#### 2021 PyCon TW Speaker

Implementation of a deep learning-based saliency detection system by Python

### 2020 HITCON Speaker

Potential Security and Privacy Issues in Novel Taiwanese National eID system

### **Awards**

2022 Best thesis award

2021 Multi-label Classification on CT Medical Imaging Competition, 3<sup>rd</sup> prize

ICH detection enhenced by asymmetric loss with CNN-LSTM approach.

### **Recent Projects**

# 2021 SUPERB: Speech processing Universal PERformance Benchmark

Entrusted by NTU, CMU, MIT, and Facebook AI to build a leaderboard web server for SUPERB Benchmark. (https://superbbenchmark.org/)

# 2021 Template is all you need: 2D to 3D reconstruction with template learned by contrastive learning

Developed a 2D to 3D reconstruction DL model leveraging the template concept.

## Education

#### 2019~2021 Master of Science (@CSIE CMDM lab) GPA 4.2 (Best thesis award)

Research topics: 3D computer vision, Machine learning, Computer security

Computer Science (bioinformatics specialization) BEBI, EECS, National Taiwan University (NTU)

#### Thesis

Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features

2014~2019 Doctor of Pharmacy GPA 4.1 (CS-related GPA: 4.3, Outstanding Graduate Award)

Clinical Pharmacy \*Also got admitted to NTU CSIE.
School of Pharmacy, National Cheng Kung University (NCKU)

### **Publications**

**Ho, M. Y.**, et al. (2022) Ultra-high-resolution unpaired stain transformation via Kernelized Instance Normalization. [under review]

\*Ho, M. Y., \*Liu, L. C., Su, B. H., Wang, S. Y., Hsu, M. T., & Tseng, Y. J. (2021). PanGPCR: predictions for multiple targets, repurposing and side effects. *Bioinformatics*, 37(8), 1184-1186. (\*equal contribution)

**Ho, M. Y.**, Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features. [unpublished manuscript] **Ho, M. Y.**, Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) A 2D camera is all you need: gait analysis with frontal-view 2D video by deep learning-based 3D estimation. [unpublished manuscript]